Gentlemen,I put it to you:
先生们 我告诉你们哟
the worst tapioca pudding is better than
the best pudding of any other flavor.
最难吃西米布丁也好过其他口味优质布丁
First off,that is axiomatically wrong
because the best pudding is chocolate.
首先 明眼人都知道这话错的
因为最好的布丁是巧克力口味
Secondly, the organic structure of tapioca
makes it a jiggling bowl of potential death.
其次 西米的有机结构使布丁
黏糊糊摇晃晃 有潜在致命危险
It is extracted from the plant...
是从植物里提取...
Hey,I'm thinking of growing a mustache.
嘿 我在考虑留点胡子
No kidding?
不是吧?
Fu Manchu, a handlebar,pencil?
傅满洲那样的? 八字胡 又尖又长?
- It's extracted from the plant.
- I'm not sure yet.
- 是从植物中提取
- 还没想好呢
You know,George Clooney has one now.
乔治・克鲁尼现在也留胡子呢
Really? I once saw him shopping
at Ralph's. He was buying tequila.
真的? 我看到过他在Ralphs超市买龙舌兰酒
You'd think a guy like that would
have some kind of booze lackey.
你以为他们会有仆人跑腿买酒吗?
All right, this is cruel.
好啦 太残忍了
We'd better let him finish
before his head explodes.
我们还是让他说完
不然人家要爆头了
All right,Sheldon, why is tap...
好吧 Sheldon 为啥西...
Tapioca is extracted from the root
of the plant manihot esculenta!
西米由食用木薯根茎提取而成
Due to a high concentration of cyanide,
由于富含高浓度的氰化物
it is poisonous in its raw form
and lethal if prepared improperly!
其本身有毒性 如加工不当即食用会致命
Feel better now?
现在爽了吧?
It is also indigenous to Brazil as is the coa
bean, from which we get chocolate, the best pudding.
同时可可豆也是巴西的
从中能提取巧克力 做最好的布丁
And you promised you
wouldn't do that anymore!
求你们别再耍我了!
Hey,Hofstadter.
嘿 Hofstadter
Hey,Kripke.
嘿 Kripke
Heard about your latest
anti-proton decay experiment.
听说你最新的反质子衰变实验了
20,000 data runs and no
statistically significant results.
收集两万数据 却没啥有用的结果
Very impressive.
灰常了得
What a jerk.
蠢货一个
Don't feel bad,Leonard. Negative
results are still results.
别气馁 Leonard 没用的结果也是结果
- Even 20,000 of them.
- All right!
- 就算两万又算啥
- 行啦!
Please don't cheer me up anymore.
求你们别在给我打气了
Come on. Don't let him
get to you. It's Kripke.
别呀 不要让他打击到你
Kripke哪根葱
Yeah,he's a ginormous knob.
对呀 大蠢蛋一个
That's why he eats by himself instead
of sitting here at the cool table.
所以他孤单用餐
而不能坐到这酷酷的桌子来
For shizzle.
说得对呀
It's true Kripke lacks the basic
social skills that we take for granted.
确实啊 Kripke确实缺乏
咱固有的那种基本社交技巧
But he also controls the new
open science grid computer
但他还操控着新的开放科学网格计算机
that I need to use to run some simulations
of structure formation in the early universe.
而我需要它来模拟宇宙早期的结构形态
Well,good luck getting time on it.
看你有没有那命用上吧
The only people he lets
use it are his friends.
他可只让他的朋友使用
Well,then, the solution is simple.
那 解决办法很简单嘛
I shall befriend him.
我去和他做朋友
Kripke!
Yeah?
啥事?
What would you say to the idea
of you and I becoming friends?
你觉得我们交个朋友如何?
I would say I have no interest
in becoming your friend.
我觉得木有啥兴趣哟
Really?
当真?
That seems rather shortsighted coming from someone
who is generally considered altogether unlikable.
你个里里外外不受欢迎的家伙
目光还真是相当短浅呀
Why don't you take
some time to reconsider?
不如重新考虑下吧?
Yeah,I'll do that.
行呀 我去想想
Well,I think we're off
to a terrific start.
看来咱这开局不错啊
荣誉出品
翻译: 王泳东 penny
校对: penny
时间轴: 咔肉肉
There you go.
好了
Now any e-mail from Wolowitz will
go right into your spam folder.
现在所有Wolowitz发来的邮件
都会直接进入垃圾箱
Thanks. I mean, the e-mail doesn't bother me as much
as the vacation pictures of him in a bathing suit.
多谢 其实骚扰邮件倒没啥
他穿浴衣的度假照比较雷人
Yeah,I got the same one, and that's
not a bathing suit. It's a tan line.
是呀 我也收到了
那可不是浴衣 是晒痕
Hello,this is Sheldon Cooper.
你好 我是Sheldon Cooper
I am leaving a message for Barry Kripke.
这是给Barry Kripke的留言
Barry,it was pleasant seeing
you today in the cafeteria.
Barry 很高兴在食堂与你邂逅
I saw that you purchased
the chef's salad.
我注意到你买了推荐沙拉
Apparently,you did not know that the chef's
salad is kitchen trickery to utilize scrap meat.
显然 你不知道推荐沙拉是
食堂的杂碎肉骗人把戏
Nevertheless, I hope you enjoyed it.
不过呢 我希望你用餐愉快
I'm following up on our pending friendship and I
look forward to hearing from you regarding its status.
我在追踪待定友谊的发展状况
期待你来电给它定位哟
Sheldon Cooper.
我是Sheldon Cooper
What's up with Ichabod?
胆小发明家又咋了?
Uh,he's trying to make a new friend.
他在交友呢
Oh,really? Well,good for him.
真的? 不错嘛
Well,unless he makes one out of wood like
Geppetto, I don't think it's gonna happen.
除非他像杰佩托做出皮诺曹
不然没戏的
How did you guys become friends?
那你们咋成为朋友的?
There was a flyer on the
bulletin board at the university:
大学公告板上的一张传单
"Roommate wanted.Whistlers
need not apply."
"招募室友 吹口哨的勿扰"
And you moved in anyway?
你就搬进去了?
I assumed he was joking.
我以为他说着玩的
You'd be surprised how many particle
physicists have a whimsical side.
你绝对想不到有多少量子物理学家
都有反复无常的一面
What about Howard and Raj? I mean,how
did he become friends with them?
Howard和Raj呢?
我是说他咋和他们好上的?
I don't know. How do carbon
atoms form a benzene ring?
不知道 碳原子是如何构成苯环的?
Proximity and valence electrons.
价电子亲近
Well,sure, when you put it that way.
是呀 你这样说也是哈
But it all worked out,right?
但相处的也不错是吧
I suppose. I do miss whistling, though.
差不多吧 尽管我很怀念口哨
Oh,come on. Really?
不是吧?
First warning.
警告一次
Penny? Penny? Penny?
Penny Penny Penny
This is for you.
给你的
Hello,Sheldon.
你好 Sheldon
What is this?
这是啥?
It's a questionnaire I devised.
我设计的调查表
I'm having some difficulty
bonding with a colleague at work
我和一位同事交友遇到点困难
so I'm doing a little research to better
understand why my current friends like me.
所以我想做些小调查 更好的了解
为什么我目前的朋友们喜欢我
Yes,well,that is a good question.
嗯 这个问题值得考虑
But is this really the
best way to figure it out?
但你确定这是最好的办法了?
I agree. The social
sciences are largely hokum.
问得好 社会学家很大程度是忽悠
But short of putting electrodes in your brain
and monitoring your response to my companionship,
但又不能插一个电极到你的大脑
探测你对我友谊问题的反应
this is the best I can do.
就这方法还凑合了
Okay,"Question one: "Rank the
following aspects of Sheldon Cooper
好 "问题1: 按吸引力程度给
Sheldon Cooper以下各方面排序
playfulness; JAVA applet writing"?
聪明 洁癖 有趣 Java程序编写?"
I know,I may have started
out with a fairly obvious one;
也许头一个问题答案过分明显
an aspect of my most
appealing trait: playfulness.
谁不知道我最吸引人的特质之一 有趣
Why don't you just go ahead
and rank that number one?
你直接把它排到1号吧
I'm afraid you're on
your own for the rest.
恐怕剩下的我不能指导你了
It should take you no
more than three hours.
用不了三个小时就可以完成
Well,wait. How many
questions are on this thing?
等下 这玩意儿有多少个问题呀?
Only 211.
区区211个
Don't worry. In deference to you, I kept them
all at a high school graduate reading level.
别担心 为了照顾你
这份高中毕业就能读懂
Thanks,pal.
还得谢你 哥们儿
You got it... buddy.
客气啥...姐们儿
Sheldon,honey,did you ever consider making
friends by being,I don't know, pleasant?
Sheldon 亲爱的 你有没有考虑过
通过让人开心来交友啊?
Well,that's certainly a
thought-provoking hypothesis.
那当然是一个发人深思的假设
May I suggest it as the
topic for your essay?
我看你论文写这题目好了
Your questionnaire, very disappointing.
你的调查问卷 十分让人失望呀
I answered every question, Sheldon.
我逢题必答呀 Sheldon
You answered the multiple
choice questions in a pattern:
你选择题很有规律嘛
A- B-A-C.A-
B-A-C.
A B B A C A B B A C
Oh,you picked up on that,huh?
你发现了哈
How could I not?
我怎么会发现不了?
Come on. There's over 200 questions.
行行好 超过200个问题
And look at some of these things.
看有些问题吧
"Sheldon is to camaraderie as
the space shuttle is to blank?"
"Sheldon之于友谊如同太空梭之于什么?"
There are a number
of acceptable answers.
这里有些适合的答案呀
For example, Near-Earth transport."
例如 C近地运输机
But certainly not Avocado rancher."
但绝对不是B鳄梨种植工
And your essay suggesting that I'd have better luck
making friends if I wait till the Cylons take over?
你在论文里还说等到赛昂人接管地球
我在交友方面会更有运气
Please.
请别
Now hold on. I put some
real work into that.
等等 那篇我可是认真写的
Yes,well,it's better
than what Wolowitz did.
是呀 可比Wolowitz好多了
He drew a raccoon with what
appears to be a distended scrotum.
他画了一个大阴囊的发情浣熊
It's kinda cute.
还真有点可爱哟
Until you get to the scrotum.
只要不看它那玩意儿
What hope do I have for establishing
new relationships given that
我怎么会有希望建立新的友情关系?
my current friends apparently could not take
a few hours out of their lives to help me?
现存的朋友们都舍不得用
他们漫长生命的少许小时来帮助我
Sheldon,I'm not going to
defend a big-balled raccoon.
Sheldon 我没打算为大蛋蛋浣熊说话
Well,I don't see how you could.
我看不出你能做到
What I'm trying to say is that maybe you can't
approach this as a purely intellectual exercise.
我想说的是 或许你不能把
这些当作纯粹智力习题来对待
What do you mean?
你什么意思?
Well,remember when you tried to
learn how to swim using the Internet?
还记得你怎么在网上学游泳吗?
Ididlearn how to swim.
我是学过游泳
On the floor.
在地板上学的
The skills are transferable.
技巧是相通的
I just have no interest
in going in the water.
我只是不想到水里去
Then why learn how to swim?
那你为啥要学游泳呀?
The ice caps are melting, Leonard.
冰盖在融化呀 Leonard
In the future,swimming
isn't going to be optional.
未来 游泳是不可避免的
But you do bring up
an interesting point.
但你给了我灵感
I don't have to break new ground here.
我用不着做新的研究
I'm sure much of the
research already exists.
肯定很多研究结果是现存的
No,no,my point is, if you want
to learn how to make friends,
不 不 我想说的是
如果你想学如何交友
then just go out to a
coffee shop or a museum.
到咖啡店或者博物馆去
Meet people. Talk to them.
认识些人 和他们交流
Take an interest intheirlives.
了解下人家的生活
That's insane on the face of it.
疯了呗
- Come on.
- Where are we going?
- 走吧
- 我们去哪儿?
You're driving me to the mall.
你载我去卖场
I'm going to acquire a book that summarizes the
current theories in the field of friend-making.
我要去买本现存交友领域的理论大全
Why don't you just lie down
on the floor and swim there?
你干嘛不直接躺地上 游过去呢?
Coping with the Death of a Loved One.
《如何面对至爱的离去》
- My condolences.
- Thank you.
- 节哀顺变
- 感谢你
- Family or friend?
- Family.
- 家人还是朋友?
- 家人
Too bad.
太遗憾了
If it had been a friend, I'm
available to fill the void.
如果是朋友 我刚好可以填补空缺
It's just as well. She
smelled like mothballs.
没关系 她满身卫生球味道
Okay,if you're gonna start sniffing
people, I'm gonna go get a hot pretzel.
好吧 要是你在这嗅人玩
我去买点热脆饼
Excuse me.
劳驾
Do you have any books
about making friends?
有交友的书吗?
Um,yeah,but they're all for little kids.
嗯 有 但都是写给小孩子的
I assume the skills can be
extrapolated and transferred.
我想技巧可以推断 道理相通嘛
I guess. They're right over
there by the wooden train set.
可能吧 就在木火车那边
I love trains.
我爱火车
I bet you do.
你当然喜欢了
Oh,my,that's awfully sticky.
哎 呀 还真粘
All right,let's see...
好了 我来瞧瞧哈...
Bernie Bunny Has Two Daddies Now.
《兔子波尼有两个爸爸了》
That's probably about
homosexual rabbits.
估计是同志兔子的故事
Gerry the Gerbil and
the Bullies on the Bus.
《沙鼠杰瑞和恶霸在公车上》
Read it. Not helpful.
读过了 没啥用
Oh,here we go.
哦 有了
Stu the Cockatoo Is New at the Zoo.
《动物园的新成员鹦鹉斯图》
"Author Sarah Carpenter
lives in Fort Wayne,Indiana
Sarah Carpenter作
现与其爱人 朋友Mark以及鹦鹉斯图
"with her husband and best
friend,Mark, and their cockatoo Stu."
居住于印第安纳州 韦恩堡
Hardly makes her an expert in
making friends, wouldn't you agree?
没有点交友专家的样子 你说是吧?
I don't like birds. They scare me.
我不喜欢鸟类 它们多吓人
Me,too.
我也是诶
Most people don't see it.
很多人都意识不到
What are you reading?
你读啥呢?
Curious George.
《好奇的乔治》
Oh,I do like monkeys.
哦 猴子我可喜欢
Curious George is a monkey.
好奇乔治就是猴子
Somewhat anthropomorphized, but yes.
算是人格化的 但没错
Say,maybe sometime you and I could go
see monkeys together. Would you like that?
或许 啥时候咱俩去看个猴子呗
你觉得好不?
Okay.
好哇
Sheldon,what are you doing?
Sheldon 你干嘛呢?
I'm making friends with this
little girl. What's your name?
我和这小女孩交朋友呢 你叫什么名字?
Rebecca.
Rebecca
Hi,Rebecca. I'm your new friend,Sheldon.
嗨 Rebecca 我是你的新朋友Sheldon
No,you're not. Let's go.
不 别搞了 走吧
- We were really hitting it off.
- Don't look up. There's cameras.
- 我俩聊得正投机呢
- 别抬头 上面有摄像头
********the "How well do
you know Sheldon" section,
我想知道哈 在"你有多了解Sheldon"那项
what did you put for
his favorite amino acid?
他最喜欢的氨基酸 你们填的啥?
- Lysine.
- 赖氨酸
Damn it, I had lysine and changed it.
完了 我本来写了赖氨酸 又改了
Oh,good,you're just in time.
太好了 时间刚刚好
I believe I've isolated the
algorithm for making friends.
我想我解开了交友解题步骤
Sheldon,there is no
algorithm for making friends.
Sheldon 交友哪有解题步骤啊
Well,hear him out. If
he's really onto something,
得了 听他讲完 要是真有啥发现
we could open a booth at
Comic-Con.Make a fortune.
咱就在动漫大会上弄个展台 赚他一笔
See,my initial approach to
Kripke had the same deficiencies
是这样 我最初和Kripke搭话就跟
as those that plagued Stu the
Cockatoo when he was new at the zoo.
鹦鹉斯图刚到公园时一样有着缺陷
Stu the Cockatoo?
鹦鹉斯图?
Yes. He's new at the zoo.
没错 他是动物园新成员
It's a terrific book.
超赞的书
I've distilled its essence into a simple flow
chart that will guide me through the process.
我摘录它的精华制作了流程图来指导我
Have you thought about putting him in a
crate while you're out of the apartment?
有没有考虑过出门时把他装进大木箱里?
Hello,Kripke? Sheldon Cooper here.
你好 Kripke? 我是Sheldon Cooper
It occurred to me that you
hadn't returned any of my calls
我想到哈 你没回我的电话
because I hadn't offered any concrete
suggestions for pursuing our friendship.
是因为我没为发展友情提出实际建议
Perhaps the two of us
might share a meal together.
或许咱俩该一起吃个饭
I see.
了解
Well,then perhaps you'd
have time for a hot beverage?
那有没有时间喝个热饮?
Popular choices include
tea,coffee,cocoa.
最受欢迎的有茶 咖啡 可可
I see. No,no,no,wait. Don't hang up yet.
了解了解 别 先别挂
What about a recreational activity?
那娱乐娱乐怎么样呢?
I bet we share some common interests.
我们肯定有共同爱好
Tell me an interest of yours.
说说你有啥兴趣爱好
Really? On actual horses?
真的呀? 骑真马?
Tell me another interest of yours.
再说个兴趣爱好
I'm sorry. I have no desire to get in
the water till I absolutely have to.
抱歉 不到逼不得已 我才不下水游泳
Tell me another interest of yours.
再说个兴趣爱好
Uh-oh,he's stuck in an infinite loop.
哦这问题要无限循环下去了
I can fix it.
我来搞定
Interesting,but isn't ventriloquism
by definition a solo activity?
有意思 但口技不是个人娱乐项目吗?
Yeah. Tell me another interest of yours.
再说个兴趣爱好
Is there any chance you like monkeys?
你喜不喜欢猴子呀?
What is wrong with you?
Everybody likes monkeys.
你咋回事嘛? 人人都喜欢猴子
Hang on,Kripke.
别挂 Kripke
A loop counter and an escape to
the least objectionable activity.
没办法时 选择不太讨厌的项目
Howard,that's brilliant.
Howard 聪明啊
I'm surprised you saw that.
你居然想到了
Gee,why can't Sheldon make friends?
天呀 Sheldon咋交不到朋友呢?
All right,Kripke, that last interest
strikes me as the least objectionable,
好了 Kripke 你刚说那兴趣爱好
是我不太讨厌的
and I would like to propose
that we do that together.
我提议咱一起去玩
Tomorrow.
明天
Yes,I'll pay. All right,good-bye.
是的 我付钱 好的 拜拜
All right. Time to learn rock climbing.
好啦 该学学攀岩了
You know,I am a fan of ventriloquism.
要知道 我超喜欢口技哟
Maybe you,me and your dummy
could go get a hot beverage.
要不你我还有你的小假人去喝个热饮
He could talk while you drink.
你喝时他表演
Nope. I wanna climb some rocks.
不鸟 我想攀岩
This appears significantly more
monolithic than it did on my laptop.
这家伙比在电脑上看起来大啊
One expects to see hominids
learning to use bones as weapons.
想看原始人怎么用骨头当武器呢
You afraid of heights, Cooper?
你恐高啊 Cooper?
Hardly. A fear of heights is illogical.
哪能啊 恐高完全不合理
A fear of falling, on the other
hand, is prudent and evolutionary.
然而害怕掉下来 才是有发展眼光的说法
What would you say is the minimum altitude I
need to achieve to cement our newfound friendship?
你说要巩固我们的友情
我最少要爬多高呀?
Come on,they have birthday parties
here. Little kids climb this.
好啦 这开生日会呢 小盆友都爬
Little kid hominids perhaps.
小原始人吧
So is this your entire job?
Your parents must be so proud.
你工作就干这点事啊?
父母一定很骄傲哈
- Let's go,Cooper.
- I'm coming,Kripke.
- 来啊 Cooper
- 来了 Kripke
Okay,the harness seems to be secure.
好的 绳子貌似很结实
A small amount of incontinence just now,
but the Web site said that's to be expected.
刚才有点不能自制
但网上说那是正常情况
this isn't so bad. It's
like vertical swimming.
也不咋难嘛 像是垂直游泳
Hey,look at you,Cooper. You're
almost halfway to the top.
嘿 瞧瞧 Cooper 都爬到一半了
I am?
是吗?
I was wrong. It is a fear of heights.
我错了 我恐高
You all right there,Cooper?
你还好吗 Cooper?
Not really.
不太好
I feel somewhat like an inverse tangent
function that's approached an asymptote.
感觉像是反正切曲线接近渐近线了
Are you saying you're stuck?
你是说你卡住了?
What part of inverse tangent function
approaching an asymptote did you not understand?
反正切曲线接近渐近线
哪个字你不明白啊?
I understood all of it. I'm
not a moron. Just keep going.
我都明白 我又不是白痴 接着爬啦
Yeah,I don't think I can.
我想我做不到
Well,then climb back down.
那就爬下去
No,that doesn't seem any more likely.
不行 更没可能了
What's your plan,Cooper?
你打算咋办 Cooper?
Well,it's not exactly a plan,
but I think I'm going to pass out.
不能算是啥打算 我想我要晕菜了
I'm sorry,can we please
just do it one more time?
抱歉 咱再做一次行吗?
Okay. One,two, one,two,three,and...
好的 一二 一二三
It's a little thing, but
you really do miss it.
小事一件 但真是怀念啊
Hello,everyone.
大家好
I brought my new friend
Barry Kripke home for dinner.
我带新朋友Barry Kripke回家吃饭了
Hello to you,too.
你们也好啊
How was rock climbing?
攀岩怎样?
He passed out.
他晕过去了
Just hung there like a big salami.
跟个意大利腊肠一样吊在那
Tha-tha-that's
where I sit.
那 那 那是我的座
Ooh,you have a special spot?
What kind of wacko are you?
你还有固定座位呢? 咋这么怪捏
How much time you got?
看你有多少时间
You want some Chinese food?
来点中餐?
Terrific. Got any dental floss?
太好了 有牙线没?
In the bathroom.
在洗手间
Be right back.
马上回来
I got to floss the Indian food out
of my teeth if I'm gonna eat Chinese.
吃中餐前要先把牙里的印度菜弄出来
Sheldon,are you okay?
Sheldon 还好吗?
Oh,yes,I pass out all the
time, but it was worth it.
哦 好呀 全晕过去了 但值了
I've made substantial progress in bonding with
Kripke, which brings me to an awkward moment.
我和Kripke的友情有了质的进展
但这也产生了一个尴尬的问题
What's that?
咋了?
Maintaing five friendships promises
to be a Herculean task,so...
维持五个朋友的友情太困难了 所以...
I'm going to have to let one of you go.
我要开除你们其中一个
Me,me,let it be me.
我 我 选我吧
Leonard,you are my roommate,
my source of transportation,
Leonard 你是我的室友 我的出行工具
and you help me fold my sheets
when they come out of the dryer.
床单烘干后你会为我叠好
You are safe.
你安全了
- Can I whistle?
- Don't be silly.
- 能吹口哨不?
- 别犯傻
Howard,you do not have a PhD; your
cologne is an assault on the senses;
Howard 你没有博士学位
你的古龙水刺激感官
and you're not available for video
games during the Jewish high holidays.
犹太重大节日期间 你不能参与电子游戏
Guilty as charged. I'm out.
我有罪啊 我淘汰了
No. You too are safe.
不 你也安全
Oh,come on. What do I have to do?
哦 不是吧 我该怎么做呀?
Okay,you know what? I
see where this is going.
好了 我知道怎么个意思了
I'm not one of you guys. I'm not
a scientist, so just tell me...
我不属于你们中的一员
我也不是科学家 直接告诉我...
Penny,Penny,Penny,everything you're saying
is true, but please allow me to continue.
Penny Penny Penny 你说的都对
但请听我说完
Raj,you're out.
Raj 你被淘汰了
That's a good question.
问的好
While you do provide a certain cultural
diversity to an otherwise homogenous group,
你的确为这个同类的小团体
注入了异域的文化
your responses to the
questionnaire were truly disturbing.
但你问卷的回答太闹心了
How could you for a moment think that
my favorite amino acid is glutamine?
你怎么会觉得我最喜欢的氨基酸是谷氨酰胺?
He had lysine,but changed it.
他写了赖氨酸 又改了
Shoulda,woulda,coulda,Raj.
早干啥了 Raj
I like to floss before I eat so my
gum pockets are open for new food.
我喜欢在吃东西前打牙线
以便牙缝迎接新的食物
Hello!
你好啊!
How did I walk past you?
我以前怎会没注意到你?
- I'm Barry.
- Penny.
- 我是Barry
- Penny
Eh,that's not a very hot name.
呃 这名字不咋性感嘛
I'm going to call you Roxanne.
我要叫你Roxanne
Ooh,pot stickers.
哦 饺子
Suddenly,I'm looking pretty good,huh?
突然前 我变得如此优质了哈?
So,Kripke,I was wondering if there's any chance you
could get me some time on the open science grid computer?
Kripke 我在想你能不能借我用用
开放科学网格计算机呢?
- No.
- No? But we're friends.
- 不行
- 不行? 我们是朋友啊
I'm sorry. No,my friend.
抱歉 不行 我的盆友
I'm confused.
搞不懂了
I was given to understand that you
allow your friends time on the machine.
我以为你会让朋友用那机器的
No,that's wrong. There's an official
schedule. I have no control over it.
不 不是那么回事 有正式安排的
我做不了主
Well,this entire endeavor seems to
have been an exercise in futility.
看来整个尝试都是徒劳了
Raj,you're back in.
Raj 你可以回来了
He likes monkeys.
他喜欢猴子
*****im credit for sticking with it.
我得表扬他的坚持精神
I didn't think he had it in him.
我看他是没那细胞
And he almost made it
to the top this time.
这次差点就到顶了啊